let's see if we can compare the mesh and
the bus throughput for a small four core
system where the traffic is evenly
distributed so that each core sends a
quarter of all the messages in the
system and the messages that each core
sends are sent round robbing to all the
other three cores so if we are core zero
we send messages to one then two then
three then one then two then three Etc
if we're core two then we send to 0 1 3
0 1 3 Etc and you can assume that this
is totally randomly distributed so that
we don't necessarily get any
synchronicity among these axises pretty
much just like a third of the traffic
sent by each core goes to each of the
other core but you can assume that it
happens willy-nilly each core sends 10
million messages per second the bus can
support 20 million messages per second
the mesh can support 20 million messages
per second per link and obviously the
four cores are going to saturate the bus
bandwidth in which case they will just
have to slow down proportionally so that
they match the bandwidth of the bus the
question for you is the speed up
achieved by switching to the mesh from
the bus is what